<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Krishna Conchem</string>

    <string name="about_us">

        \t\t\t\t\t\t\tKrishna Conchem Products Pvt. Ltd. (KCPPL) is involved in manufacturing and development of Specialty Construction Chemicals since 1981. KCPPL has over the years offered many an innovative solutions to concrete corrosion, repairs, rehabilitation and construction problems.

\n\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tMost of our products have been put to use by various clients ( private, public sector, government, defence etc. ) across the country. Among others the projects include:
Protection of concrete against corrosion incorporating Bipolar Concrete Penetrating Corrosion Inhibiting Admixtures.

\n\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tRolex replica watches this year launched the "log Pearl Oyster replica watches Perpetual Lady-type" new watch is equipped with three replica handbags39 mm case, 3235-type movement, and its louis vuitton replica eye-catching outer gorgeous mosaic louis vuitton replica gradations of 48 breitling replica square cut sapphires: Blue fade to purple, blue replica watches gradient green, orange to yellow gradient, each with a beautiful.In addition, last year launched a cartier replica classical style Cellini series, this year crowned by omega replica a jewel, a single outer ring and the outer ring diamond double two styles to choose from, the outer ring and the outer ring styles from the classic hermes replica which double diamond ring triangular grooved outer ring, the Rolex classic elements and new design perfect fusion.
Protective coating and rehabilitation of large number of bridges, jetties, dams.
Seismic retrofitting of structures
Strengthening of turbo generator foundations
Structural strengthening and repairs of corrosion damaged buildings, aqueducts, bridges.
Adhesives, Sealants, Mortars, Grouts, Bonding Agents and Heritage Coatings.
Food grade coatings.

\n\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tOur main strength lies in dovetailing structural engineering knowledge with the polymer / cement chemistry to offer need specific solutions. Active research and development , coupled with strong research link up with premier research institutes in the country enable us to offer latest technologies at affordable costs to customers.

    </string>

    <string name="research">

        \t\t\t\t\t\t\tThe company is active in the area of research and development at its inhouse laboratory. All products are indegeniously developed with support from institutes like IIT, UDCT, and CSIR affiliated laboratories.

\n\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tResearch and Development and QC departments play a proactive role in meeting the company’s quality policy. We have a state of the art research and development laboratory, which helps us in meeting the dynamic demands of the market.

\n\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tOur contemporary cutting edge technology processes and equipments, along with a team of dedicated trained professionals ensure that customers always get consistent quality products. The effort to maintain the highest standards of quality involves the whole organization, from Research and Development to production.
    </string>

    <string name="address">

        Krishna Conchem Products pvt. Ltd.

\n1-2, Bldg. 6, Sector 3,
\nMillenium Business Park,
\nMahape, Navi Mumbai - 400 705
\nMaharashtra - INDIA

    </string>

    <string name="phone">
        Telephone
        \n022- 2778 29 23 / 24
    </string>

        <string name="email">
        Email Address\ninfo@krishnaconchem.com
    </string>

    <string name="website">
        Website\nwww.krishnaconchem.com
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
